SOLD ME
BROTHERS
MY OWN
SILVER.
FOR
THEY BOWED AT
LATER
YEARS
FEET,
MY
BREAD
BEGGING FOR
THE RULER WAS
KNOWING
NOT
ME.
WITH
DID
WATCH WHAT GOD
EVIL.
THEIR
PIECES OF
FOR TWENTY
SOLD
SILVER.
CONDEMNED.
FALSELY
DUNGEON.
THROWN IN A
RIGHT
PHARAOH'S
THEN LIFTED TO
SAVIOR
THE
HAND AND MADE
WHO
BROTHERS
OF THE VERY
AWAY.
ME
THREW
BECAME A ROAD
PIT
EVERY
CLIMBED.
THAT
A
ONLY
BUT I WAS
SHADOW.
BROTHER.
GREATER
THERE CAME A
FOR TWENTY;
SOLD
I WAS
JUDAS,
BY
JESUS WAS SOLD
OWN TWELVE,
HIS
ONE OF
THIRTY.
FOR
CONDEMNED,
FALSELY
KILLED,
THAN ANY PIT
LOWER
BROUGHT
DEATH
INTO
DOWN
TO SAVE THE
RAISED
THEN
WORLD,
TO
EVEN
PARDON
OPENING HIS
WHO DROVE THE
MEN
THE
NAILS.
WITH BREAD,
DID
WHAT I
WITH HIS OWN
DID
HE
BLOOD,
OF
IN THE PLACE
DYING
WHO HATED HIM.
SINNERS
THE
CALLS:
HE
ME,
UNTO
COME
AND
YE THAT LABOUR
ALL
LADEN,
ARE HEAVY
WILL GIVE YOU
I
AND
REST.
WHO
BROTHER
YOU ARE THE
HIM.
SOLD
OUT NO
JESUS HOLDS
YET
SWORD
BLOOD,
HIS
ONLY
THROWN WIDE.
ARMS
AND
CLEAN ENOUGH
YOU'RE
NOT WHEN
NOW,
ARE.
YOU
AS
FORGIVES
BROTHER WHO
TRUST THE
STILL.
YOU